export const questions = [
  {
    question:
      "Which major city put the first urban tram line into service in 1832?",
    optionOne: "Vienna",
    optionTwo: "London",
    optionThree: "Berlin",
    optionCorrect: "New York",
  },
  {
    question: "By what name is the patella more generally called?",
    optionOne: "Paella",
    optionTwo: "Spread",
    optionThree: "Shoulder blade",
    optionCorrect: "Kneecap",
  },
  {
    question: "Which gas planet is the largest planet in the Solar System?",
    optionOne: "Neptune",
    optionTwo: "Uranus",
    optionThree: "Saturn",
    optionCorrect: "Jupiter",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the common, more popular name for an orca?",
    optionOne: "Calf",
    optionTwo: "White shark",
    optionThree: "Beluga",
    optionCorrect: "Killer whale",
  },
  {
    question: "What are plants that lose their leaves in autumn called?",
    optionOne: "Evergreen",
    optionTwo: "Carnivorous",
    optionThree: "Coniferous",
    optionCorrect: "Deciduous",
  },
  {
    question: "How many keys are there on a piano keyboard?",
    optionOne: "80",
    optionTwo: "100",
    optionThree: "62",
    optionCorrect: "88",
  },
  {
    question: "In what year were the first Winter Olympics Games held?",
    optionOne: "1974",
    optionTwo: "1890",
    optionThree: "1954",
    optionCorrect: "1924",
  },
  {
    question: "What was the first ever toy to be advertised on television?",
    optionOne: "Barbie",
    optionTwo: "Dominoes",
    optionThree: "Polly Pocket",
    optionCorrect: "Mr. Potato Head",
  },
  {
    question: "How many vaginas does a female kangaroo have?",
    optionOne: "One",
    optionTwo: "Two",
    optionThree: "Three",
    optionCorrect: "Four",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of these countries have a flag that is different on either side?",
    optionOne: "Bahamas",
    optionTwo: "Costa Rica",
    optionThree: "Denmark",
    optionCorrect: "Paraguay",
  },
];
